<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kaho Abe 阿部香穂</title>
    <link>http://kahoabe.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kaho Abe 阿部香穂</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 20:23:59 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://kahoabe.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Frankenstein AI</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/frankenstein-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 20:23:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/frankenstein-ai/</guid>
      <description>planchettes.
   Summary Influenced by the collaborative engagement of the Ouija Board Planchette, these controllers are designed to be used by 2 users together, to glide over a touch-sensitive screen. It allows the users to engage with each other, to collectively arrive at an answer to the questions being asked. Users must rest their fingers upon the perforated metal components of the controller in order for it to be sensed by the technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hotaru</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/hotaru/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/hotaru/</guid>
      <description>By Martin Christopher Welker for Invisible Playground at Playpublik Festival Krakow 2014, Flickr, licensed under CC BY-NC-SA 2.0
   Summary Hotaru is a 2-person cooperative task-based game, where the players play the role of the last remaining lightning bugs in a fantastical world, in their last stand against an invisible enemy. One player creates lightning, accumulating it in a tank, through gestures. Once the tank is full, then transfers the lightning to the other player by holding hands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ninja Shadow Warrior</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/ninja-shadow-warrior/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 20:23:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/ninja-shadow-warrior/</guid>
      <description>Ninja Shadow Warrior from Kaho A on Vimeo.
Summary Ninja Shadow Warrior is a stand alone photo booth arcade game using the Kinect camera, computer and a hacked closet light button built into a custom game cabinet. The palace is under attack and the player must use his/her ninja magic to hide by “becoming” objects. The player must fill out the silhouette of a randomly chosen object from the ninja palace as accurately as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hit Me!</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/hit-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2011 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/hit-me/</guid>
      <description>Hit Me! (2011) from Kaho A on Vimeo.
Summary Hit Me! is a two-player hyper-interactive, physical game that tests speed, agility and the ability to take good snapshots. Utilizing wireless technology and incorporating the concept of the metagame, Hit Me! encourages face-to-face real-world interactions, not only by the players but also by the spectators.
The object of the game is to hit the opponent’s button on top of the head.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mary Mack 5000</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/mary-mack-5000/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2010 19:56:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/mary-mack-5000/</guid>
      <description>Mary Mack 5000: Everyone can play it! from Kaho A on Vimeo.
Summary Mary Mack 5000 is a fast-paced, competitive, technologically enhanced twist on the classic schoolyard hand clapping game. Strap on your special MM5000 gloves and show off your speed, accuracy, and style! This is a collaborative project made with Lina Fenequito, with music from Ray Mancini and Sergey Popovich.
These days, most games are played on computers and consoles, often alone or with people online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selfiestick Deathmatch</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/selfiestick-deathmatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/selfiestick-deathmatch/</guid>
      <description>Judge&amp;#39;s panel.
   Summary Selfie Deathmatch is a two person competitive physical game where the players stand in a very small circle each holding a selfiestick loaded with a camera phone. The phones automatically take a photo on a timer, and then the photo is judged. The number of faces counted is the base score. The photos are then tweeted (https://twitter.com/selfiedm), and the number of likes and retweets adds to the base score.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spiritus Chronomatix</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/spiritus-chronomatix/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/spiritus-chronomatix/</guid>
      <description>Summary Narrative-based augmented reality puzzle game using the Google Tango as a tool to travel through time, and to see into the ghost world. There is an angry spirit in the room, turning on lights, making sounds, and setting off the Reliever contraption.
  Support Sam Sadtler worked on the wireless communications between the objects. This project was supported by NYU Game Innovation Lab and NYU Tisch Experiments in Storytelling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wizard&#39;s Hand</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/wizard-hand/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2015 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/wizard-hand/</guid>
      <description>Glove embedded with Leap Motion.
   Summary At the museum, you are curiously drawn to the dusty remains of a skeletal hand, tucked safely behind a glass case, that legend tells once belonged to a powerful wizard. You instinctively put it on, ignoring the sign, &amp;ldquo;DO NOT TOUCH!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; and the world changes. As you walk through the museum, the artifacts come to life, some carrying spirits with timeless grudges against the wizard, whose hand now has become yours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Happies</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/little-happies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2014 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/little-happies/</guid>
      <description>Little Happies at 2016 GaymerX.
   Summary Little Happies are things that make bring people comfort and happiness in small ways. This includes anything from cute plushies that you might keep by your computer, or a small cupcake in your favorite flavors, or a goofy shirt that you love to wear. Little Happies the game is an over-the-top, bordering on ridiculousness, nod to all the Little Happies out there in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mitgenommen</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/mitgenommen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2014 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/mitgenommen/</guid>
      <description>Crafted button using a wooden door knob, a nail, rubberbands, conductive fabric and a flip flop.
   Summary Designed for a hidden park tucked away in the middle of the city, we hand-made various playfully mysterious wooden boxes &amp;ndash; some that light up, some that move, some that make sounds &amp;ndash; from found materials, reclaimed wood and hacked electronics. Designed for the people who would hang out at the park, we hoped to create playful experiences and curiosity through these boxes that eventually would disappear into the space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Window Vistas</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/windows-vistas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2014 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/windows-vistas/</guid>
      <description>uh-oh... this video player is unsupported! Recording of screen experience.   Summary Window Vistas is a game made during the Train Jam 2014 on the Amtrak Zephyr train. During this 52 hours adventure from Chicago to San Francisco for the Game Developer&amp;rsquo;s Conference, we were inspired by the ever-changing scenery we saw through the window. We rode through Illinois, Nebraska, Colorado, Nevada and California. Players can enjoy the vistas and take photos from our window too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pandemojis</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/pandemojis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2014 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/pandemojis/</guid>
      <description>Summary Pandemojis is a social classroom game using a webcam and facial recognition software that helps players to identify emotions in themselves. The player must first catch an emoji that is falling from the top of the screen onto their head. Once they are &amp;ldquo;wearing&amp;rdquo; the emoji, they are then asked to make a gesture or pose that expresses the emotion they are &amp;ldquo;wearing&amp;rdquo;. Then the classroom is asked to guess the emotion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mecha Mouse</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/mecha-mouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/mecha-mouse/</guid>
      <description>Mecha model.
   Summary Mecha Mouse is a robot made from hacked consumer products and cardboard, driven by 5 elite, super-intelligent mice. This model was built for a multi-player VR game, specifically to help design the character, which was later recreated in Blender 3D and developed in Unity.
Gallery     Family of naked mice. NSFW.
      Wire frame and wood base.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shake It Up!</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/shake-it-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/shake-it-up/</guid>
      <description>Summary Remember when you were a kid, you&amp;rsquo;d shake up a can of soda and hand it to an unsuspecting friend. And when your friend opened it, they&amp;rsquo;d be doused in an explosion of soda? Well, this game is based on that nostalgic experience. One player is asked to shake the soda can and the place it on the table. All players must wait until it is safe to pick up the soda.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portable Projection Dome</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/portable-projection-dome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 20:23:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/portable-projection-dome/</guid>
      <description>Working on game with Jack Langerman. Photo by Cherise Fong.
   Summary This is a very large, hand-made, quarter-sphere projection dome that measures 10 ft. high and 20 ft. wide. It was made from a beachball pattern making spreadsheet found on the internet, which I unfortunately lost the link for. I used stretchy knit projection fabric, cotton herringbone taping, fiber glass replacement camping tent poles, upholstery thread, and some thick rope.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discreet Interfaces</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/discreet-interfaces/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2005 20:23:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/discreet-interfaces/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Kate Kunath, taken at the 2005 MIT Seamless Fashion Show.
   Summary It is often taken for granted that our clothing serves a crucial connection to the world around us. Our clothing is rich in subtle messages; about who we are, who we want to be, and our roles in society. Discreet Interfaces enables the wearer to carry and utilize the technology without compromising any of these messages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BallAR</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/ballar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/ballar/</guid>
      <description>Title screen.
   Summary Ramsey and I were invited to participate in the Google AR Core Game Jam that took place in September of 2019 in Los Angeles. We made a multiplayer AR tennis type game where the room becomes a ball court. First the player must scan the room, and then enter each players names. Then the game begins! Each player&amp;rsquo;s name is called, and must take turns hitting the virtual ball.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safer Sex Shuffle</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/safer-sex-shuffle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2014 20:23:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/safer-sex-shuffle/</guid>
      <description>Jimmy holding a stop sign, and also some zany characters from the game.
   Summary Safer Sex Shuffle is a casual browser-based puzzle game where the player must make tile combos in order to progress in the game, racking up points. The tiles consist of body part tiles (butts, mouths, hands, penises and vaginas) and barrier tiles (dental dams and condoms). In order to make a combo, the player must select body part tiles with the correct barrier in between if needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MicroμN</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/microun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2014 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/microun/</guid>
      <description>Portraits of a rulers. Photos by Ida Benedetto.
   Summary MicroμN is an experimental roleplaying game inspired by the numerous uninhabited islands that lie in the waters around New York City, where players became the rulers of their own lands. First starting in person at our headquarters on Governor&amp;rsquo;s Island, we registered each player and took portraits of them. The game then continued virtually for a month via email, where the rulers would battle it out to take over other islands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robots in the Sky</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/robots-in-the-sky/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2014 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/robots-in-the-sky/</guid>
      <description>Title screen.
   Summary Robots In The Sky is a two-player shooter game where players use their eyes to aim and shoot at virtual flying robots. Players take on the role of a defensive mech and deflect evil flying robots by looking them, causing the mech’s laser eyes to fire and shoot them out of the sky. The eyes of each player are tracked using Tobii hardware and fed into the Unity game as the sole input.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Wake the Bear</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/dont-wake-the-bear/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 20:23:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/dont-wake-the-bear/</guid>
      <description>Don’t Wake the Bear trailer from Kaho A on Vimeo.
Ramsey Nasser (game design, programming)
Kaho Abe (game design, graphics)
Francis Hsueh (sound design)
Summary “Don’t Wake the Bear” is a multiplayer game designed to be played on a single gaming device by up to 8 players at a time. The game can be played with friends and family, young and old, in any social space — ideally, at a party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bunny Blur</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/bunny-blur/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/bunny-blur/</guid>
      <description>Initial sketch.
   Summary In the world of cut throat bunny street racing, where do you stand?
Bunny Blur is a work-in-progress stand alone car racing arcade game. I am experimenting with storytelling through the custom dashboard and the arcade cabinet itself. The game is influenced heavily by personal experience playing 80&amp;rsquo;s racing arcade games, goofy retro cartoons, and the Fast and Furious franchise. The intent here is to make a fun and engaging racing game that plays with the line between physical and digital experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mario Ball</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/mad-fun-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 20:23:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/mad-fun-show/</guid>
      <description>Summary Mario Ball is oversized physical controller for the original Mario Brothers game that requires 2 people to hold it up and use it. The controller uses 90 magnetic reed switches which are triggered when a magnetic ball (dressed up as Mario) is rolled around. The Arduino and 6 multiplexers are used in addition to the magnetic reed switches. The maze senses where the ball is and Mario appears at the corresponding location on the original Mario Brothers screen interface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cupcake Machine</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/cupcake-truck/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/cupcake-truck/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Ida Benedetto.
   Summary The Cupcake Machine is a playful experience combining audience participation, performance, puzzles and cupcakes encased neatly in an unmarked truck.
The Cupcake Machine is an glorious old cupcake making machine, which is first presented to the unsuspecting audience members on a tour hosted by an enthusiastic Cupcake Machine representative. But the tour eventually goes terribly awry when the machine breaks down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Casual Encounters the Game</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/casual-encouters/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2011 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/casual-encouters/</guid>
      <description>Screenshot of start screen.
   Summary Casual Encounters the Game is the brainchild of the brilliant Jeff Crouse. It is a party game where two people compete to match correctly the image with the Craigslist casual encounter ad title. The image is slowly revealed, rewarding the ability to imagine the rest of the image as quickly as possible.
A bunch of us teamed up with him at the Creator&amp;rsquo;s Project Art Hack Weekend that took place at Eyebeam in April 2011.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Noisegenerator</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/noise-generator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2009 20:23:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/noise-generator/</guid>
      <description>Makes lots of fun noise!
   Summary A 4-step sequencer, made from Forrest M. Mims III&amp;rsquo;s sound synthesizer circuit that uses two 555 timer IC chips, AKA the Atari Punk Console. There are additional switches that allow for changing the sequence pattern, as well as one that switches between the sequencer and a dynamic noise generator controlled by a photoresistor. The custom face plate was made using a semi-transparent acrylic sheet, stenciled and laser-etched from the inside, and then painted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haptic Music Gloves</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/haptic-music-gloves/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2005 20:23:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/haptic-music-gloves/</guid>
      <description>Project version shown at 2nd Beijing New Media Arts Exhibition &amp;amp; Symposium 2005 Music: All 5 tracks by sound artist Jenks Whittenburg
Summary A handshake is a common way to greet and communicate people in many social situations. It is a simple ritual that carries understanding and trust. Music is an universal language. It transcends language barriers, creating opportunities for people to communicate even if they do not understand each other’s spoken words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh Shit!</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/oh-shit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2005 20:23:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/oh-shit/</guid>
      <description>Drawing the board was almost as fun as playing the game.
   Summary Oh Shit! is a narrative-based board game about the stresses of buying gifts for loved ones for the holidays, while being sick from eating bad food. The player who is done buying all the gifts on their list first is the winner. Please excuse the potty humor!
More Information  Rules and Objectives [pdf]  Gallery     I am sorry the theme is so gross.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sleeve Station</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/sleeve-station/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2005 20:23:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/sleeve-station/</guid>
      <description>The punk sleeve from the Sleeve Station. Touch the spikes to control the mp3 player.
   Summary The Sleeve Station is an interactive installation demonstrating that we do not have to sacrifice the social messages in our clothing when wearing clothing embedded with technology. There are 4 sleeves in varying fashion styles &amp;ndash; punk, athletic, classic and casual. Each sleeve has its own unique, discreet interface using objects that are already found on clothing, like snaps and buttons, that allow the user to control one mp3 player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Euthanasia</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/digitial-euthanasia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2005 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/digitial-euthanasia/</guid>
      <description>Summary Digital Euthanasia is a 30 second science fiction radio play about the first cat to be digitally euthanized. Made with voice recordings, composed music and Pro Tools.
 Voice of Cat Owner: Daniel London Voice of Cat: Sammy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Circle of Friends</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/circle-of-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2004 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/circle-of-friends/</guid>
      <description>User flow-chart.
   Summary Circle of Friends is a pre-facebook, online social photo sharing game made with PHP and MySQL.
A circle of friends is formed, the moderator decides on a theme, and then all the members of the circle must post a photo in order to make the round of photos available. If any of the members do not post a photo, the circle will “die” and the photos never become visible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Devastator</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/the-devastator/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2003 20:23:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/the-devastator/</guid>
      <description>Interfaces that make face-to-face experiences.    Summary The Devastator is a sound machine that 2 people use facing each other. Each user can use their interface to generate their own tone. It is meant to be used without instructions, and with some experimentation, the users are able to see that not only do the controls manipulate their own sound, but has a secondary impact on the other user’s sound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fashion Design</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/fashion-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2009 20:23:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/portfolio/fashion-design/</guid>
      <description>Boned and corseted sleeveless wedding dress that I designed and constructed in 2005.
   Summary Prior to 2010, I was a fashion designer for 14 years. I&amp;rsquo;ve worked in women&amp;rsquo;s, men&amp;rsquo;s and children&amp;rsquo;s wear, for global labels to smaller couture labels. I&amp;rsquo;ve also made many dresses for special occasions &amp;ndash; wedding and evening dresses. I specialized in custom corseted strapless dresses with boning. And while I haven&amp;rsquo;t done any fashion design recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve found ways of incorporating aspects of it into my games in the form of wearable game controllers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Website</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/blog/2018-02-121-new-wesbite/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/blog/2018-02-121-new-wesbite/</guid>
      <description>The significance of each item on the border.
                              I&amp;rsquo;ve finally finished my new website! I&amp;rsquo;d be lying if I said that building this website has been easy for me. I&amp;rsquo;ve spent about a year trying out new tools, restarting, re-designing over and over again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/about/</guid>
      <description>“If going vroom makes the car go forward, maybe saying vroom, backwards would make it back up. Moorv.” -- Beverly Cleary, Ralph S. Mouse Short Bio Kaho Abe is a game designer and media artist based in NYC interested in improving social and personal experiences through the use of technology, fashion and games. She designs games and builds custom controllers with the hope to bring people together in new ways, face to face, in public spaces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>http://kahoabe.net/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kahoabe.net/education/</guid>
      <description>&#34;Play is often talked about as if it were a relief from serious learning. But for children play is serious learning.&#34; -- Mister Rogers Teaching Artist Teaching is synonymous to sharing my practice as an artist. Consequently all my teaching content is based on the tools and the methods that I use to make art. My goal is to explore self-expression, encourage curiosity and to help find the clarity and enjoyment in the act of creating and building what is imagined.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>